<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://pseudosurfer.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://pseudosurfer.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-05-19T14:33:41+01:00</updated><id>https://pseudosurfer.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Pseudo Sufer</title><subtitle>The personal site of Justin Bennewith. Pseudo Sufer is the name for photography and Sudo Surfer is the name for 3D and other artworks.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Starting Again</title><link href="https://pseudosurfer.com/2021/04/24/Starting-again.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Starting Again" /><published>2021-04-24T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-04-24T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://pseudosurfer.com/2021/04/24/Starting-again</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pseudosurfer.com/2021/04/24/Starting-again.html">&lt;p&gt;After an accident, I’ve lost access to my hard drive so while I wait to access it, I’m starting again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My 2014 MacBook Pro died after liquid got spilled on it so I’ve bought myself a new &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.apple.com/uk/mac-mini/&quot;&gt;M1 Mac Mini&lt;/a&gt;.
I’ll get a hard drive enclosure to access the old hard drive but in the meantime I’m recreating my site.
I did not save my files to GitHub properly and I guess this little incident will be a good lesson on how to keep all my important stuff together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since starting my Jekyll site I’ve added and removed multiple plug-ins and assets. By starting again I can have a fresh install from which to work. For instance I’m using a gallery creator that builds static html gallery pages. The creator of that script uses Bootstrap and so instead of fighting against it I’ve decided to start using Bootstrap from the beginning.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">After an accident, I’ve lost access to my hard drive so while I wait to access it, I’m starting again.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Adding a hype banner</title><link href="https://pseudosurfer.com/2021/04/01/Adding-a-Hype-banner.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Adding a hype banner" /><published>2021-04-01T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-04-01T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://pseudosurfer.com/2021/04/01/Adding%20a%20Hype%20banner</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pseudosurfer.com/2021/04/01/Adding-a-Hype-banner.html">&lt;p&gt;I’ve changed the home page by adding an animated banner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used &lt;a href=&quot;https://tumult.com/hype/&quot;&gt;Tumult Hype&lt;/a&gt; to create a HTML animation for
my home page banner.
It’s pretty straightforward figuring out how to use Hype if you’ve used
After Effects or other animation type software in the past.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used &lt;a href=&quot;https://http://blender.org&quot;&gt;Blender&lt;/a&gt; to create my rolling text. I could’ve used Blender for a lot more of the banner but since I’m trying to learn how to use Hype, I decided to do just the main text piece. Blender saves animations as movie files or individual PNGs which is the preferred method to use in case Blender crashes or in case you need to pause your rendering you can just pick up where you left off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hype lets you add a sequence of images as a sprite sheet. Hype exports the final piece as an index.html file along with all the supporting pieces in a folder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding your final piece to your Jekyll set-up is a little more difficult. Hype uses vanilla javascript and it outputs a minified version of the javascript file which helps it to load faster. However all the paths to the images, sounds, svg, and javascript files are written inside the minified javascript file which requires you to go in and add your Jekyll required path like :”/assets/images” to the paths of each file. I think I had a total of six which need to be changed.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I’ve changed the home page by adding an animated banner.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Finally all set up</title><link href="https://pseudosurfer.com/2021/03/13/Finally-all-set-up.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Finally all set up" /><published>2021-03-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pseudosurfer.com/2021/03/13/Finally%20all%20set%20up</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pseudosurfer.com/2021/03/13/Finally-all-set-up.html">&lt;p&gt;Pseudo is my Photography side of my site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s taken me 5 months and 4 days to get this all set up and ready to start writing posts.
Actually with Covid shut-downs and immigrating to Scotland all tied in, it’s only actually
taken me a week to figure this out. I’ve dabbled with Ruby for more than a few years on and
off, most of the time trying to figure out Rails at the same time.
I found Sinatra a lot more adaptable to my simple needs Jekyll appears to tick all my boxes.
Free static site hosting on Github pages makes all this a no brainer.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Pseudo is my Photography side of my site.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sudo is 3d art</title><link href="https://pseudosurfer.com/2021/03/13/Sudo-is-3D-art.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sudo is 3d art" /><published>2021-03-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pseudosurfer.com/2021/03/13/Sudo%20is%203D%20art</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pseudosurfer.com/2021/03/13/Sudo-is-3D-art.html">&lt;p&gt;Sudo is my 3D artwork side of my site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been using Blender on and off for about 10 years but it’s really only been
since version 2.5 onwards that I’ve tried to really get into it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really enjoy polygon modelling. I used Rhino for a short period several years ago
and I know that I really enjoyed using its nurbs and bezier approach so I guess
it just happens that I enjoy whatever tool I have in my hands.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Sudo is my 3D artwork side of my site.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Getting set up</title><link href="https://pseudosurfer.com/2020/09/09/Getting-set-up.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Getting set up" /><published>2020-09-09T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-09-09T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://pseudosurfer.com/2020/09/09/Getting%20set%20up</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pseudosurfer.com/2020/09/09/Getting-set-up.html">&lt;p&gt;It’s time to set this site up using Jekyll hosted on Github Pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope this turns out well.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">It’s time to set this site up using Jekyll hosted on Github Pages.</summary></entry></feed>